(Penny:)-Hi, guys.
-Hello.
(Penny:)Yo, Raj, talk to me.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, just screwing with you.
(Penny:)Hey, Howard,
why haven't you called Bernadette?
(Howard:)Did she say something?
(Penny:)Said she hasn't heard from you.
I thought you liked her.
I do, you know,
but she wants a commitment...
(Howard:)...and I'm not sure she's my type.
(Penny:)She agreed to go out with you for free.
What more do you need?
(Howard:)Look, Bernadette is really nice.
(Howard:)I just always thought when I finally
settled down into a relationship...
(Howard:)...it would be with someone,
you know, different.
(Penny:)Different how?
(Howard:)Well, you know, more like Megan Fox
from Transformers...
(Howard:)...or Katee Sackhoff
from Battlestar Galactica.
(Penny:)Are you high?
(Leonard:)You'd have a better shot with the
three-breasted Martian from Total Recall.